vpnexperts.com 2018-05-29

# Privacy Policy - VPN Experts

We (“ **Company** ” or “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”) adhere to the practices detailed in this Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** “) in respect of your access and use of our website: http://www.vpnexperts.com ( **“Site” or “Website”** ) and the Service provided (as defined in our [Terms of Service](https://www.top5-webcams.com/terms-and-conditions/)). We have designed this Privacy Policy so that you can clearly understand our privacy practices, including how or why we collect, share and use our users’ data. We recommend you to read this Privacy Policy carefully prior to accessing or using our Service. This Privacy Policy is part of our [Terms of Service](https://www.top5-webcams.com/terms-and-conditions/) (collectively “ **Terms** ”) and constitutes a legally binding agreement between you and us. Definitions herein shall have the same meaning as defined therein.

By using or accessing the Site and Service, you hereby agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Any use or continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement and consent to this Privacy Policy and any amendments therein. You accept the terms of this Privacy Policy by simply using the Service or the Site. If you do not agree to be bound by these terms, you are prohibited from accessing, viewing or using the Site or the Service. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to revise or update these this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes shall be effective upon publication of the amended Terms (the last revision will be reflected in the “Last Modified” heading). Your continued use of the Service thereafter constitutes you consent to such changes and you agree to be bound by them. Please make sure to review our Privacy Policy periodically.

You represent and warrant that you are at least 18 years of age, we do not use the Services to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 18. We reserve the right to request proof age in order to verify that minors under the age of eighteen (18) are not using the Services. In the event that we become aware that a user under the age of 18 has shared any information, we will discard such information. If you become aware or have any reason to believe that a child under the age of eighteen (18) has shared any information with us, please contact us at [marketing@searchvision.com](mailto:marketing@searchvision.com).

**_Data Collection_**

We may collect information from you automatically during your access or use of the Service or when you voluntarily choose to provide us with information, all as detailed below.

We collect solely non-identifiable aggregated information (“ **Non-Personal Information** “) such as: technical information transmitted by your device, your aggregated use of the Service, statistics, type of browser, language and the time and date you access and use the Service, Website navigation, duration and clickstream, statistical browsing information, approximate geographical location, IP address, etc. Please note, we consider this data to be Non-Personal Information, however, in some countries and jurisdictions some of this data, such as IP address, might be considered as identifying and “Personal Information”.

In addition, if you contact us you will voluntarily provide us with identifying or personal information, such as your name, email address or other contact details (“ **Personal Information** ”). We do not use this information except to reply to your compliant or requirement, we further do not combine Personal Information you may provide voluntarily with the Non-Personal Information.

**_Purpose of Use_**

We use information solely to provide the Service, the Non-Personal Information is used to track users’ movements around in order to ensure that our Site and Content are presented as effectively as possible, and according to users’ preferences as well as to perform research, analytics or for statistical purposes. The Personal Information voluntary provided by you is used solely to correspond with you and comply with your requests.

**_Third Party Content and Sites_**

The Service and Content include links to the Service Provider Sites (all as defined and detailed in the [Terms of Service](https://www.top5-webcams.com/terms-and-conditions/)). These Service Providers and their applicable sites and content contain privacy practices that may differ from ours. We are not, and won’t be held responsible to such privacy practices. Thus, we recommend you to carefully review the applicable third-party privacy policy once you leave our Site via any link directing to Third Parties’ Sites.

**_ _** ** _Cookie Policy_**

We use Cookies and other technologies (e.g. web beacons, pixels, etc.), as we gather some information automatically, by ourselves or by using third party service providers (i.e., Google Analytics). “ **Cookies** ” are small text files that are placed on your device by a web server when you access our Service, for more information about cookies please review: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). You are able to disable some cookies through your device or browser settings. Please note that, if you choose to disable cookies, some features of our Services may not operate properly. Third parties (i.e., Google Analytics) may use cookies, scripts or web beacons for the purpose of tracking and analyzing your use. Additional information with respect to Google’s use of the data from our use of Google Analytics Cookies, is available in Google’s policies located at: [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners). We also recommend you to read about Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs available at: [ ](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.

**_Sharing Data with Third Parties_**

The data we collect may be used or shared in any of the above circumstances, as well as **_(i)_** for the purpose of providing and improving our Services; **_(ii)_** internally within the Company to conduct business and marketing analysis; **_(iii)_** we may disclose your information to third parties subject to your consent; **_(iv)_** we may share your information in order to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; **_(v)_** we may share your information for the purpose of enforcing our agreements and policies as well as to establish, exercise or defend our rights; **_(vi)_** we may share your information in order to prevent third party infringements, including intellectual property and privacy rights; and **(vii)** we may share the data other third parties, including without limitations the Service Providers, ad networks, advertising companies, media and other interested parties.

In addition, we may share your information with a parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control solely if and when applicable or necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy including in any corporate transaction event. We may share information, in the event of a corporate transaction (e.g. sale of a substantial part of our business, merger, consolidation or asset sale), provided however, that our affiliated companies or acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy;

**_ _** ** _Data Retention and Security_**

We retain the information we collect solely for as long as required to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected.  However, in some circumstances we may retain the information we collect for longer periods, for example, when we are required to do so in accordance with legal, tax and accounting requirements, or if we reasonably believe, at our discretion, that we need to obtain an accurate record of your correspondence or any dealing with us, for example, in the event of any complaints. We use high security techniques to prevent your information from being accessed without authorization, improperly used or disclosed, unlawfully destructed or accidental loss. However, although we make best efforts we can’t provide 100% security and we cannot be held responsible for unauthorized or unintended access that is beyond our control. If you believe that your privacy was treated not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, or you have reasonable concern with that any person attempted to abuse our Service, please contact us [marketing@searchvision.com](mailto:marketing@searchvision.com).

**_ _** ** _Users Rights_**

Even after you have provided your consent to this Privacy Policy, you may change your mind. If you do, you may easily opt out of the data collection related to our Service by changing your browser settings and disabling or blocking cookies. You may also contact us [marketing@searchvision.com.](mailto:marketing@searchvision.com) Further, as we use third party retargeting services, you may also opt-out directly from third party retargeting cookies or other ad-technology trackers through self-regulator services like the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“ **NAI** ”) website – [NAI consumer opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (“ **DAA** ”) website – [DAA opt-out page](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**_Transfer of Data_**

We may store or process your information in the United States or in other countries. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (“ **EEA** “) we will take appropriate measures to ensure that your information receives an adequate level of data protection upon its transfer outside of the EEA. If you are a resident of a jurisdiction where transfer of your data requires your consent, then your consent to this Privacy Policy includes your express consent for such transfer of your Personal Information.

**_ _** ** _Do Not Track Disclosure_**

The Website or our Services does not respond to Do Not Track signals. For more information about Do Not Track signals, please see: <http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>_._

**_Contact Us_**

If you have any questions in relation to this Privacy Policy or you wish to exercise any of your rights, please contact us at: [marketing@searchvision.com](mailto:marketing@searchvision.com).
